华纳兄弟电影公司
可以开始了
Start talking.
明日边缘
不知道能不能播出去
I'm not sure if we're on the air.
应该说 这是一系列爆炸
This is a series of explosions...
突发新闻
我们刚刚得知 这是一起严重的事件
We're being told this is a major incident.
这场严重的突发事件
The emergency is a major incident.
突发新闻：德国受到不明攻击
有人看到耀眼的闪光和橙色的火焰
Bright lights and an orange glow.
撞击产生爆炸的瞬间
That was the moment the meteor hit.
汉堡现场画面
毫无疑问 这是一场严重的入侵事件
It does now appear to be a major attack.
汉堡告急
圣格奥尔
诺伊施塔特
汉    堡
法国总统弗朗索瓦·奥朗德
自从五年前降落在汉堡市境外
Since they landed outside Hamburg five years ago...
它们已经横扫了整个欧洲大陆
they have steadily advanced across Europe.
爆炸投影点
我们已经损失了几百万人
We've suffered millions of casualties.
英国
英吉利海峡
法国
丹麦
德国
捷克
瑞士
立陶宛
波兰
白俄罗斯
俄罗斯
斯洛伐克
匈牙利
罗马尼亚
摩尔多瓦
乌克兰
德国
瑞士
捷克
波兰
斯洛伐克
匈牙利
摩尔多瓦
乌克兰
白俄罗斯
各国政府要员目前已经开始撤离了
The evacuation of key government officials continuing.
俄罗斯
英  国
英吉利海峡
欧洲议会疏散
法  国
很显然 我们无力阻止它们
Nothing has stopped their advance.
正在发生：毁灭性打击横扫欧洲
在人员方面 欧洲已经付出了高昂的代价
In human costs, the Europeans have paid the highest price.
天空高清新闻
联合防御部队
英国伦敦   现场直播  法国巴黎
模仿者突破巴黎屏障
它们有模仿能力 甚至超越我们的各种行为
They have the ability to mimic and even anticipate our actions.
如果不能在法国打败它们
If we do not defeat them in France...
《恐怖袭击警报
最新消息
外星人入侵仍在继续
就得在伦敦街头跟它们较量
we'll be fighting them in London
焦点新闻：遭受入侵五年之际 新的军事计划出台
然后是纽约 东京
then New York, then Tokyo.
焦点新闻：布里格姆将军 联合防御部队指挥官
这是一场生死之战
All of humanity's at stake.
五年后 我们终于取得了胜利
After five years we finally have a victory.
凡尔登大捷：数年溃败后联合防御部队首尝胜利
这是从凡尔登传回的画面
These pictures are just in from Verdun.
凡尔登大捷
天空高清新闻
凡尔登现场
值得称道的是这次胜利伤亡少 损害低
One of the striking things was how low casualties were and how little damage...
加入联合防御部队
应该说这的确是一场了不起的胜利
We have seen a stunning victory here today.
布里格姆将军：我们必胜
凡尔登之后的
最新策略
你怎么才能让人们相信 这场战争我们必胜
How do you convince people that this is a fight that can be won?
这是外星人对全球的侵略战争
This is an alien invasion in a global war.
有了新型战甲技术和很少的训练
With the new jacket technology and limited training...
威廉姆·凯奇少校
美军媒体专员
我们就能创造出超级战士
we've been able to create super-soldiers.
参军人数激增
瑞塔·沃塔斯基 就是凡尔登的天使
Look at Rita Vrataski, the Angel of Verdun.
力量
他们称她为凡尔登的天使
They're calling her the Angel of Verdun.
力量
速度
我希望你加入
联合防御部队
她被看成是这场战争的新希望
She is seen as the new hope for this war.
的确是非同凡响
It's extraordinary.
莫斯科视频连线                                          华盛顿特区
响应凡尔登天使
数千人竞相参军
有了新型战甲技术和很少的训练
With the new jacket technology and limited training...
瑞塔·沃塔斯基一天就可以杀掉几百个模仿者外星人
Rita Vrataski was able to kill hundreds of mimics on only her first day.
战争的形势发生变化了吗
Is the tide of this war changing?
军方把这次胜利归功于一项新技术
The Army attribute this success to a revolutionary new technology:
新型战甲技术
The Exosuit jacket.
联合防御部队
没有你就没有明天
新闻故事
威廉姆·凯奇少校
头条新闻
贾克·塔珀
她一天就可以杀掉几百个模仿者外星人
She was able to kill hundreds of mimics on only her first day in combat.
如果全军都是这样的战士
Imagine an army of Rita Vrataskis.
我们在英吉利海峡抵挡住了它们
We're holding them back at the English Channel,
突发新闻：全面反击迫在眉睫  百万军队紧急动员
问题是能挡多久
but for how long?
这种观点过于轻率 人们难免对此持怀疑态度
This is dangerous talk. People are suspicious about this invasion.
超过17个国家加入了联合防御部队
Over 17 nations have joined the United Defense Force...
以期将其击退 一劳永逸
which hopes to push them back.
我们控制住了局面
We've got them contained.
有了这项新技术 绝对能打败它们
And with this new technology, we're gonna defeat them.
威廉姆·凯奇少校
歼灭计划将会成为人类历史上规模最大的机甲战斗
Operation Downfall is going to be the largest mechanized invasion in history.
我们一定会胜利
We will be victorious.
来吧
We fight.
没什么可怕的
That's what we do.
伦   敦
我是威廉·凯奇少校 美国军方媒体的
Major William Cage, United States Military Media.
欢迎您来伦敦 少校
Welcome to London, major.
联合防御部队总部
将军可以见你了
The general will see you now.
谢谢
Thank you.
行动计划是这样的
Operation Downfall.
整个联合防御部队
The entire UDF,
从法国 地中海 斯勘的纳维亚直入
invading from France, the Mediterranean, Scandinavia...
缓解东部前线的压力
relieving pressure on the eastern front...
好让俄国和中国部队把敌人赶回去
allowing the Russians and Chinese to push the enemy back.
在中部会师
We all meet in the middle...
一路把这帮该死的家伙斩尽杀绝
exterminating this mimic scourge along the way.
很多优秀的战士明天会战死 少校
A lot of good soldiers are gonna die tomorrow, major.
等硝烟散去 裹尸袋被送回来的时候
When all the smoke clears and the body bags start coming home,
就会需要有个人来背黑锅
people look for someone to blame...
比如说 我
someone like me.
希望能有人为我说句公道话
Ideally, I'd prefer a different scenario.
请吧
Please.
也许能写本畅销的回忆录
A best-selling memoir, perhaps.
或者从此走上政坛
Maybe a career in politics?
对我来说 第一反应就是
Off the top of my head,
应该强调你胸怀大志
I would go with the sense of manifest destiny.
白手起家 却又平步青云
Rags to riches. Rapid rise through the ranks.
天生的领导者
Born to deliver us.
人们
And the people,
就喜欢听这类话题
well, they love that sort of thing.
你理解错了 少校
You misunderstand.
我不是请你推销我 而是这场反击战
I didn't ask you here to sell me. Sell the invasion.
好的
Okay.
船一小时后出发 摄像团队已经就绪
You ship for the coast in one hour. Your camera crew is standing by.
第一轮攻击将在海滩展开
You'll be on the beach with the first wave.
对不起 第一轮攻击在海滩 你是说去
I'm sorry, the first wave? The beach? You mean...
- 前线 - 法国
- the front? - France.
卫星显示 海岸线上有小股敌人
Satellites show minimal enemy movement on the coast.
会有些抵抗
Little resistance.
将来跟孩子们也有的炫耀了
A little excitement, something to tell your grandchildren.
我理解你这种自信 将军
While I appreciate the confidence, general...
我就是为了回避那些才做这个的
I do this to avoid doing that.
在大学 我曾经是预备役军官
I was in ROTC in college.
战争爆发后
The war broke out,
我放弃了自己的广告公司
I lost my advertising firm...
来到军队
and here I am.
所以 我有我的专长
You know, I do what I do,
你有你的使命
and you do what you do.
不过
But...
我不算是个战士 真的
I'm not a soldier, really.
对 你当然不是
No, of course you're not.
所以我才让你跟几十万士兵在一起
I'm embedding you with several hundred thousand who are.
我很荣幸 将军 但我承受不起
While it is an honor, I'm afraid I'm gonna have to decline.
我见血就晕 被纸割伤都受不了
Can't stand the sight of blood. Not so much as a paper cut.
呃 不过
Uh, but, uh...
不过 既然话说到这儿了
sitting here thinking about this...
我倒觉得有几个人
a couple of names come to mind...
可以向你推荐一下
that I feel I could recommend to you.
这不是商量 少校 是命令
It's not an offer, major. It's an order.
将军 别忘了我是一名美国军官
General, I am an officer in the United States military.
很抱歉 你没权利命令我
You don't even have the authority.
我跟你的长官说过了
I have spoken to your CO.
你现在受我指挥
You are now under my command.
当然你还保留目前的军衔
You will retain your present rank of course.
我秘书会再跟你详谈
My secretary has all the details.
好好干吧 少校
Do a good job, major.
祝你好运 你可以走了
Good luck. You are dismissed.
将军
General?
我已经鼓动了几百万人加入你的军队
I just inspired millions of people to join your army.
当裹尸袋被运送回国
And when the body bags come home and they're looking...
肯定要有个人出来背黑锅
for someone to blame,
你觉得我该怎么写
how hard do you think it would be...
才能让人们不骂你
for me to convince people to blame you?
我敢肯定 将军也不想那样吧
I'd imagine the general would prefer to avoid that.
你是在威胁我吗 少校
Are you blackmailing me, major?
我只是
I would prefer...
不想明天到海滩 去拍摄那些勇士的英雄壮举
not to be filming acts of heroism and valor on that beach tomorrow.
那好吧
You won't be.
我很高兴能顺利解决问题
I'm glad we could, uh, work this out.
那我告辞了 将军
Now if you'll excuse me, general. I...
谢谢
Thank you.
把他抓起来
Arrest this man.
什么
What?
嗨 嗨
Hey! Hey!
站那儿别动
Stop right there!
站住
Hey! Stop!
快闪开
Get out of the way!
闪开
Out of the way!
抓住他
Hold it!
向左转 走
Left flank, march!
起步 走
Forward, march!
向后转
About-turn!
商店将在10分钟后关门
Supplies closing in 10 minutes.
希思罗
全
金属
贱人
站起来 废物
On your feet maggot!
不许这样跟长官说话 中士
That is no way to address an officer, sergeant.
我就是这样对待新兵的 你这种蠢货只配这样对待
It's how I address a slack-jawed recruit before I bust his hole
急了我还踢你 废物
with my boot heel, maggot.
先等等 中士
Hold up there, sergeant.
要帮忙吗 长官
Can I help you, sir?
这是哪儿 中士
Where the hell am I, sergeant?
希思罗前线保障基地
Forward Operating Base Heathrow.
你是跟新兵一起来的
You just came in with the fresh recruits.
我看着像新兵吗
Do I strike you as a fresh recruit?
不 长官 你不像
No, sir, you do not.
我是威廉姆·凯奇少校
My name is Major William Cage.
- 是美国军官 - 军官
- I'm an American officer. - Officer?
这里是新兵营
This is processing.
军官不会来这儿的
There's no officers here.
交给我吧 中士
I got this, sergeant.
你怎么会跑到新兵营来的
How the hell did you end up in processing?
怎么了 扑克之夜 单身派对
What was it? Poker night? Bachelor party?
对你来说没有区别 中士
If it's all the same to you, sergeant...
我想跟华盛顿的指挥官解释一下
I'd like to explain that to my commanding officer in Washington.
如果你能告诉我电话在哪儿
If you'll take me to a phone...
你不知道吗
Haven't you heard?
战斗随时都可能开始
We're T-minus-Haul-Ass-H-Hour.
我们要打法国
We're fixing to invade France.
整个基地都封闭了 不准通电话 接打都不行
This whole FOB's on lock down. No calls, in or out.
- 你叫法莱尔 - 没错
- Name is Farell. - That's right.
二等中士法莱尔
Master Sergeant Farell.
美国人
You're an American.
不 先生 是肯塔基人
No, sir. I'm from Kentucky.
好吧 好 看看我
Okay. Well, look at me.
再看看这里
And look at where I am.
我是被迫的
I've been railroaded.
很显然 我不属于这里
It's obvious I don't belong here.
所以求你了 中士
So please, sergeant,
想办法让我打个电话
there has to be a way I can make a phone call.
我会把你带到地方
I'll get you sorted out, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
这边走
Right this way.
你来自肯塔基的哪儿 中士
Where you from in Kentucky?
一个叫科学山的小镇 听说过吗
Little town called Science Hill. Heard of it?
刚听说
I have now.
- 那你从哪儿来 - 新泽西州的克兰伯里
- Where you from? - Cranbury, New Jersey.
克兰伯里 那儿是不是出玻璃
They grow a lot of cranberries there?
西红柿 盛产西红柿
Tomatoes. Best you ever had.
那为什么叫克兰伯里
Why they call it Cranberry, then?
你们那儿为什么叫科学山
Why they call it Science Hill?
从没问过 无所谓
Never asked. Don't care.
你先请
After you.
你不是带我去找电话吗 中士
You're not taking me to a phone, are you?
不 当然不
No, I am not.
看来你说的话 只有你的名字是真的
Seems about the only honest thing you said to me so far is your name.
这上面说你是个逃兵
Says here you're a deserter.
说你被指控冒充美国军官
It says here you were caught impersonating an officer.
还说你会试图往外打电话
It says here you'd likely try to make an outside call,
甚至还会威胁到行动的安全
compromise security of this operation.
只要能逃避战斗 什么都干得出来
Anything to get out of combat duty tomorrow.
但这些都不会发生
But that's not gonna happen.
不会
Ever.
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage.
人言可畏
Rumor is a terrible thing.
不等到晚上
Come nightfall,
这些人对你的看法就会达成一致
these men will all reach the same conclusion.
你是个自私的胆小鬼
That you're a coward and a liar,
为了活命 什么都干得出来
putting your life above theirs.
好消息是 你还有希望 二等兵
Good news is there's hope for you, private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
也是一个大熔炉 能锤炼出真正的英雄
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
战场上没有高低贵贱之分
The one place where all men truly share the same rank...
无论你来的时候是什么样的废物
regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.
都听着 这位是二等兵凯奇
Squad! This here is Private Cage.
二等兵凯奇 这是J小队
Private Cage, J Squad.
那不是军官制服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
这可不是军官的待遇
Those sure ain't officer cufflinks.
看来大家早上过得都非常充实
I see everyone is having a productive morning.
看到你们这水准的人让我倍感自豪
You know, it gives me a swell of pride knowing soldiers of your...
因为明天是你们去冲锋陷阵
caliber will be leading the charge tomorrow.
长矛之尖
Tip of the spear.
利剑之刃
Edge of the knife.
尖利
Crack of my...
个屁
ass.
该死
Oh, shit.
二等兵 基梅尔
Private Kimmel,
我对在军营里赌博是什么观点
what is my view of gambling in the barracks?
你不喜欢 法莱尔中士
You dislike it, Sergeant Farell.
南希 我为什么不喜欢
Nance, why do I dislike it?
这会鼓励大家靠运气取胜 而不是靠自身素质
It entertains the notion our fate is in hands other than our own.
在命运面前 我们永远不变的态度是什么
And what is my definitive position on the concept of fate,
告诉我
chorus?
纪律严明 时刻准备 做命运的主人
Through readiness and discipline, we are masters of our fate.
你们也许会觉得这很荒唐
You might call that notion ironic.
但相信我
But trust me,
你们会理解的
you'll come around.
二等兵凯奇是个逃兵
Private Cage is a deserter.
我要你们每一个人亲自负责教导他
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.
明天早上6点 他必须进入备战状态
He will be combat ready at 0600 tomorrow.
备战状态
Combat ready?
二等兵凯奇幻想自己不属于这里
Cage is under the delusion he does not belong here.
我们必须制止他的这种幻想
We must dissuade him of this delusion.
如果他试图逃跑
If he tries to run,
你们可以随便揍他 揍到他没法站着撒尿
feel free to dissuade him until he can't piss standing up.
中士 你听我说
You have to listen to me.
我不可能在这儿备战
I will never be combat ready.
我嫉妒你 凯奇
I envy you, Cage.
明天早上你将接受洗礼 重获新生
Tomorrow morning, you will be baptized. Born again.
体能训练 10分钟
PT! Ten minutes!
服装不配套
You're not in uniform...
二等兵
private.
请所有备战小组成员做好准备
Could all combat-ready squadrons proceed...
早上好
It's a new day, people.
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
这世界只要我们做一件事
The world expects only one thing from us:
取得胜利
That we will win.
爆炸物
利刃高爆雷
此面朝向敌方
来吧 基梅尔 好戏开始了
Come on, Kimmel, let's have it!
我的天呐  基梅尔
Oh, for christ sake, Kimmel.
这样多自在
I got to be free, man.
好了 开始了 我得穿的正式点儿
Let's get this show on the road. I gotta suit up.
那是什么鬼声音
What's that noise? That...
我们走
Let's go.
听着 伙计 我真不想穿这玩意儿
Listen, I've never been in one of these.
是啊 我以前还从来没玩过双飞呢
I've never been with two girls at the same time.
如果你能帮我找俩来 我绝对能搞定
You can bet when that day comes, I'll make it work.
基梅尔
Kimmel.
是格瑞夫
It's Griff.
格瑞夫 对 没错
Griff. Griff. You bet.
你想一想 伙计
Just think about this, man.
我可能会伤着别人 所以
I could hurt somebody with it.
有保险的 放心吧
Not with the safety on, you won't.
可
But...
保险在哪儿
Where is the safety?
这就对了
Exactly.
严禁穿越
到时间了
It's time.
我的天呐 是全金属贱人
Bloody hell, it's the Full Meta...
快走
Move.
- 格瑞夫 - 中士
- Griff. - Sarge?
照顾一下二等兵凯奇
Take care of Private Cage.
什么 全天
What, all day?
我有预感 用不了全天
Something tells me it won't be nearly that long.
凯奇
Cage!
- 凯奇 - 凯奇
- Cage! - Cage!
我们丢了德国
We lost Germany.
又丢了法国
We lost France.
今天再输 那就没必要再打了
If we lose today we won't get to fight another.
我知道你们的压力很大
I know the pressure on you is enormous.
2分钟后空降
Two minutes to drop.
害怕是正常的
It's all right to be scared.
记住 没有恐惧就没有勇气
Remember, there's no courage without fear.
嗨
Oi!
伙计
Oi, mate!
你的衣服好像不太对劲儿
I think there's something wrong with your suit.
是啊 里面装的是死人
Yeah. There's a dead guy in it.
出去后可要小心点儿 长官
Hey, watch your back out there, sir.
没人会罩着你的
No one else will.
1分钟 1分钟后空降
One minute! One minute to drop!
嗨
Hey.
- 嗨 - 怎么了
- Hey! - What?
告诉我怎么打开武器上的保险
How do I turn the safety off of my weapon?
什么
What?
怎么打开武器上的保险
How do I turn the safety off...?
我的上帝
Oh, my God!
全体准备
Get ready!
30秒后空降
Thirty seconds to drop!
听我指令
On my mark!
做好空降准备
Stand by to deploy!
拉动空降索 要记住
Activate drop lines. Remember...
快跳
Drop now!
快跳 跳
Let's drop! Drop!
跳
Drop!
快跳 跳
Drop! Go!
跳 快点儿跳
Go, let's go!
快跳
Come on!
跳 跳
Drop! Drop!
凯奇 不跳会死的
Cage! Drop or die!
我们成功了
We made it!
感谢上帝 我们成功了
Thank God, we made it!
选择语言
Select language.
【 选择语言 】
【 日  语 】
需要支援 我们需要支援 需要支援
We need help! We need it now! We need help!
这是怎么了
What the...?
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage!
你走错方向了
You're going the wrong way.
会失去战斗的机会
You're gonna miss your moment.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
它们不应该知道我们来
They're not supposed to know we're coming.
我们进了屠宰场 老兄
We walked into a slaughterhouse, man.
这就是个屠宰场
It's a slaughterhouse!
冷静点儿 别慌 福特
Pull yourself together! Ford!
都起来 伙计们
On your feet, people!
都精神点儿
Get in line!
南希 马上搜索敌情
Nance, get me a sitrep.
保险 我的保险
Safety! My safety!
格瑞夫 福特 掩护侧翼
Griff, Ford, cover the flank!
保险 我的保险
My safety. My safety.
怎么打开我的保险
How do I get my safety...?
- 什么情况 南希 - 找到踪迹了
- I'm waiting, Nance! - I got traces!
500米外 正在迅速逼近
Five hundred meters and they're coming in fast!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
让开
Out of the way!
不想死就打起精神
Look alive if you wanna stay that way!
攻击姿势
Firing positions!
上
Move!
【 安全警告 】
它们来了
Here they come.
来势汹汹 数量多的惊人
Mean as hell and thick as grass.
等它们再靠近点儿
Wait till they're right on us!
【 安全警告 】
再等几秒钟
Few more seconds!
【 安全警告 】
嗨
Hey!
重新装弹
Fall back!
【 重新装弹 】
重新装弹
Reload.
此面指向敌方
赶快归队
On your feet, maggot!
别等着我踢你屁股 废物
Get in line before I bust your hole with my boot heel, maggot!
先等等 中士
Hold up there, sergeant.
要帮忙吗 长官
Can I help you, sir?
法莱尔中士
Sergeant Farell. Is it...?
没错 就是我
That is my name.
我知道怎么回事了
I think I get it.
说说吧
What was it?
扑克之夜 单身派对
Poker night? Bachelor party?
我也不知道
You know, I'm not sure.
常有的事
It happens.
我会带你过去的 长官
I'll get you sorted out, sir.
我来帮你拿
Let me take those for you.
今天 什么日子
What day is it?
对你
For you?
是审判日
Judgment Day.
好消息是你还有希望 二等兵
The good news is there's hope for you, private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
是一个大熔炉
The fiery crucible in which...
- 能锤炼出真正的英雄 - 能锤炼出真正的英雄
- ...the only true heroes are... - The only true heroes are forged.
你竟然敢打断我 二等兵
Did you just interrupt me, private?
中士
Sarge, you're...
如果我说出来 你肯定不会相信
You're not gonna believe what I'm about to tell you.
当然不信
No, I'm not.
刚才说到哪儿了
Now, where was I?
一个大熔炉
The fiery crucible.
一个大熔炉 能锤炼出真正的英雄
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
战场上没有高低贵贱之分
The one place where all men truly share...
无论你来的时候是什么样的废物
the same rank, regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.
- 欢迎来到地狱 兄弟 - 都听着
- Welcome to hell. - Squad!
这位是二等兵凯奇
This here is Private Cage.
二等兵凯奇 这是J小队
Private Cage... J Squad.
那不是军官制服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
这可不是军官的待遇
They sure ain't officer cufflinks.
要知道 看到你们这批水准的人让我倍感自豪
You know, it gives me a swell of pride knowing soldiers of your caliber...
因为明天是你们去冲锋陷阵
will be leading the charge tomorrow.
长矛之尖 利剑之刃
Tip of the spear, edge of the knife.
尖利个屁
Crack of my ass.
二等兵基梅尔 我对在军营里赌博是什么观点
Private Kimmel, what is my view of gambling in the barracks?
你不喜欢 法莱尔中士
Dislike it, sergeant.
南希 我为什么不喜欢
Nance, why do I dislike it?
这会鼓励大家靠运气取胜 而不是靠自身素质
It entertains the notion our fate is in hands other than our own.
在命运面前 我们永远不变的是什么
And what is my definitive position on the concept of fate,
告诉我
chorus?
纪律严明 时刻准备 做命运的主人
Through readiness and discipline, we are masters of our fate.
你们也许会觉得这很荒唐
You might call that notion ironic.
但相信我 你们会理解的
Trust me, you'll come around.
我的天呐 基梅尔
Oh, for christ sake, Kimmel.
这样多自在
I gotta be free, man.
好了 伙计
All right, man.
开始了 我得穿的正式点儿
Let's get this show on the road. I gotta suit up.
启动
Disengaged.
【 开启状态 】
你在搞什么 老兄
Hey, what the hell's wrong with you, men?
难道你以前没穿过这个
Haven't you ever been in one of these before?
也许吧
Maybe.
知道保险在哪儿吗
Know where the safety is?
不太清楚
I'm not sure.
很好
Good.
我知道你们的压力很大
I know the pressure on you is enormous.
2分钟后空降
Two minutes to drop.
害怕是很正常的
It's all right to be scared.
记住 没有恐惧 就没有勇气
There's no courage without fear.
嗨
Oi!
伙计
Oi, mate!
你的衣服好像不太对劲儿
I think there's something wrong with your suit.
是啊 里面装的是死人
Yeah. There's a dead guy in it.
出去后可要小心点儿 长官
Watch your back out there sir.
- 没人会罩着你 - 没人会罩着你
- No one else will. - No one else will.
行啊 贱货
Jinx, bitch!
听我指令 做好空降准备
On my mark! Stand by to deploy!
拉动空降索 30秒后空降
Activate drop lines, 30 seconds.
- 要记住 一着陆 - 嗨
- Remember, hit... - Hey!
跳 快跳
Go! Go!
我们成功了
We made it!
小心背后 小心
Behind you! Look out!
小心
Incoming!
我中弹了 我中弹了
I'm hit. I'm hit.
很严重吗
How bad is it?
是不是 流了很多血
Is there... Is therea lot of blood?
你胸口有一个洞
You have a hole in your chest.
- 真的 - 对
- Really? - Yeah.
你竟然拿走了
Did you just take my...?
我的电池
My battery... battery?
不
No, no, no.
该死的
Holy fuck...
站起来 废物
On your feet maggot!
法莱尔中士
Sergeant Farell!
Sergeant Farell.
有什么事吗 长官
Can I help you, sir?
我是威廉姆·凯奇少校 美军媒体专员
My name is Major Bill Cage. I'm U.S. Army Media Relations.
我没参加派对或玩扑克
I was not at a bachelor party or a poker game.
你的左侧口袋里有一封传令
You have an order
说我是个逃兵 被指控冒充军官
that says I'm a deserter caught impersonating an officer.
但是上面并没说
But what it doesn't say is...
你是来自肯塔基的科学山镇 二等士官长法莱尔
your name is Master Sergeant Farell from Science Hill, Kentucky.
如果你给我半分钟时间解释
If you give me 30 seconds to explain how I know that,
你就有可能救下这个基地里的所有士兵
you may save the lives of every soldier on this base.
你一定要听我说 它们知道我们的计划
You have to listen to me! They know we're coming!
正等着我们呢
They're waiting for us!
我去过了 我看见了一切
I have been there! I've seen it!
这就是送死 必死无疑
You're all doomed! You're doomed!
好 没事 没事了
Okay. Okay. Okay, I'm fine. I'm fine.
我没事 我很好
I'm fine. I'm fine.
是J小队 对吗
This is J Squad. Yes?
对 就是J小队
This is J Squad, yes.
不相信我是吧 没关系
Not that I should know that, but okay.
你们有人曾见过我吗
Have any of you met me before?
根本不认识你
Bitch, I don't know you.
这就对了 没错
Exactly! Yes!
谢谢
Thank you.
你叫南希 你是比伯尔
Your name is Nance. You're Bible.
基伯尔 基梅尔
Kibble... Kimmel!
屁股穿战甲 没错吧
You fight balls out. Literally.
福特 斯金纳 格瑞夫
Ford. Skinner. Griff.
你是
You're...
他不爱说话
He doesn't talk much.
这床底下藏着一副牌
But there's a card game under the bed.
嘴可真欠 混蛋
Thanks a lot, asshole.
基梅尔是一副同花顺
Kimmel's working on a flush.
是梅花 是方块
Spades. No, clubs.
你正打算收拾他们
You're gonna make them eat those cards.
我没说错吧
Am I right?
现在
Now...
我说的话听上去好像很疯狂
what I'm about to tell you sounds crazy.
但是真的
It's true.
你们一定要听我说
And you have to listen to me.
这对你们来说 很重要
Your very lives depend on it.
1分钟
One minute!
什么 他在说什么
What? What is he saying?
南希 他在说什么
Nance! What is he saying?
听我指令 做好空降准备
On my mark! Stand by to deploy!
飞船马上就要爆炸了
The ship is about to explode!
【 开  启 】
我们成功了
We made it!
感谢上帝 我们成功了
Thank God, we made it!
别等着我踢你屁股 废物
Before I bust your hole with my boot heel!
我们成功了
We made it!
感谢上帝 我们成功了
Thank God, we made it!
抱歉 我是在救你
I'm sorry. I'm trying to save you.
这就是场屠杀
We're getting slaughtered.
你得把我们从海滩上弄走
You need to get us off this beach.
得马上离开 这里马上就会爆炸
We have to go. This drop ship is about to explode.
得赶快离开这儿
We have to go now.
等等
Wait.
来吧
Come on!
快点儿
飞船马上要爆炸了
This ship is going to explode!
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
醒了以后来找我
Find me when you wake up.
什么
What?
等你苏醒后来找我
Come find me when you wake up.
站起来 废物
On your feet maggot!
别等着我踢你屁股 废物
Get in line before I bust your hole with my boot heel!
好消息是你还有希望 二等兵
Good news is there's hope for you, private.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
也是一个大熔炉 能锤炼出真正的英雄
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
战场上没有高低贵贱之分
The one place where all men truly sh...
听着 这位是
Squad, this here is...
二等兵凯奇 你们都是J小队的
Private Cage. And you must be J Squad.
幸会了 各位
It's good to meet you.
那不是军官制服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
- 这可不是军官的待遇 - 肯定不是
- These sure ain't officer's cufflinks. - Those sure...
钥匙
Keys in the...
应该在左边口袋
left pocket, probably.
二等兵凯奇是个逃兵
Private Cage is a deserter.
我要你们每一个人亲自负责教导他
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.
明天早上6点 他必须进入备战状态
He will be combat ready by 0600 tomorrow.
二等兵凯奇幻想自己不属于这里
Private Cage is under the delusion he does not belong here.
我们必须制止他的这种幻想
We must dissuade him of this delusion.
如果他试图逃跑 你们可以揍他
If he tries to run, feel free to dissuade him...
不 不 我不会离开大家
Oh, no. I'm not gonna run.
- 绝对不会 - 直到他没法站着撒尿
- Not a chance. - Till he can't piss standing up.
谢谢 法莱尔中士
Thank you, Sergeant Farell.
那接下来呢 体能训练
What next? A little, uh, PT?
体能训练 10分钟
PT! Ten minutes!
左
Left!
你们是干什么的
What are you? Sound off!
我们是战士
I'm a warrior!
- 战士该干什么 - 战斗
- What do warriors do? - Kill!
- What are you gonna do? - Kill!
- 战士该干什么 - 战斗
明天是我参加过的第20场战斗 兄弟
It's gonna be my 20th battle tomorrow, mate.
不可能有20场 老兄
You haven't been in 20 battles, mate.
当然有
I have too.
明天一到海滩 你肯定会吓傻的
You're gonna dump your load the second we hit the beach tomorrow.
拜托 你们俩能不能闭上臭嘴
Why don't you get yourselves a cup of shut-the-hell-up?
真幽默 小妞
You funny, girl.
我打赌 明天我会破纪录的
I bet I set a record tomorrow.
是掉头逃跑最快纪录吧
Fastest time running backwards, Ford,
别踩到自己拉的屎
slipping in your own shit.
别扯那些没用的
Knock off the grab-ass!
闭嘴 中士
Grab this, sarge!
立定
Hold up!
二等兵 趴下 给我做
Private, drop and give me...
50个 是吗
Fifty, sarge?
没错
That's right.
50个
Fifty.
全体
Platoon!
给我做50个俯卧撑
Drop and give me 50!
你们托了二等兵凯奇的福
Compliments of Private Cage.
谢谢 中士
Thank you, sarge.
- 一 - 一
- And one! - One!
- 二 - 二
- And two! - Two!
- 三 - 三
- And three! - Three!
你到底在搞什么鬼
What the hell were you thinking?
你还有希望 二等兵
There's hope for you, private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
- 三 - 三
- Three! - Three!
- 四 - 四
- Four! - Four!
- 五 - 五
- Five! - Five!
严禁穿越
你好 沃塔斯基中士
Excuse me. Sergeant Vrataski.
你好
Excuse me.
沃塔斯基中士
Sergeant Vrataski?
你好
Excuse me.
什么事 谁让你跟我说话了
Yes? Who said you could talk to me?
难道我脸上花了吗 士兵
Have I got something on my face, soldier?
你让的 是你
You did. You did.
明天在海滩
Tomorrow. At the beach.
我见过你
We meet.
你让我苏醒之后来找你
You said to find you when I wake up.
你肯定知道些什么
You do know what's happening to me.
跟我来
Come with me.
听着
Now.
除了我不要跟任何人说起这件事
You don't talk to anyone about this but me.
否则 最好的结果是被关进精神病院
The best-case scenario is you're gonna end up in a psych ward.
最坏的结果 是被当试验品解剖
Worst case, you'll get dissected for study.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
- 说话 - 明白
- Yes? - Yes.
第一次死是什么情况
First time you died, what happened?
- 你杀了个外星生物 - 是的
- You killed a mimic? - Yes.
- 描述一下 - 很特别
- Describe it. - It was different.
体型大
It was bigger.
蓝色的
Bluish.
你被它的血液喷到了
And you got covered in its blood.
说的一点没错 是的
As a matter of fact, I did.
它们事先知道了 所以明天在海滩
They know we're coming on the beach tomorrow.
是场屠杀
It's a slaughter, isn't it?
你是怎么知道的
How do you know this?
你能不能 等等
Could you just...? Wait!
等等 等等
Wait. Wait.
能不能请你跟我解释一下 这到底是怎么回事
Would you explain to me what the hell is happening.
我曾经也经历过
What happened to you happened to me.
但后来又没了 就这样 行了
I had it. I lost it. Okay?
我觉得你现在这样挺好 我怎么摆脱这个
That's great. There's a cure. How do I get rid of this?
我需要你的帮助
First, I need your help.
我能怎么帮你
Help with what exactly?
打赢战争
Winning the war.
跟我来 快
Let's go! Come on!
武器维修
瑞塔 什么意思
Rita, what is this?
瑞塔 你来这儿干什么 你该先告诉我的
Rita, What are you doing here?  You gotta give me some warning.
他是谁
Who's this?
他就是我 凡尔登之前的
He's me. Before Verdun.
他会帮我们的
He's gonna help us.
什么 你是说他是
What? You mean he's...?
对
Yes.
什么时候死的 在哪儿
When did he die? Where?
在海滩 明天
On the beach. Tomorrow.
我在背后竖起了几根手指
How many fingers am I holding up behind my back?
我怎么会知道
How should I know that?
好吧
Okay.
这是我们第一次这样对话
So this is the first time we've had this conversation.
给他试试这个
You should try this on him.
这是什么鬼东西
What is that?
没用的
It doesn't work.
他预见什么了吗
Has he had any visions yet?
什么预见
Visions of what?
还得需要点时间
There's still time.
- 是的 - 时间 等等 很抱歉
- Yes. - Time? Look, I'm sorry.
他是谁
Who is this?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是卡特博士
I'm Dr. Carter.
粒子物理 高等微生物学
Particle physics. Advanced microbiology.
他是唯一相信你经历的人
He's also the only other person who'll believe what's happening to you.
没人比他更了解模仿者外星人
No one understands mimic biology better than him.
他是白厅的首席分析师
He's a top analyst at Whitehall.
那已经是遇见瑞塔之前的事了 现在我只是个
Well, I mean, I was until I met Rita and now I'm just...
精神有问题的机械师
a "mechanic with psychiatric delusions."
卡特 给他看看
Carter. Show him.
那好吧
Yeah, right.
首先
Right. Well, first of all...
你不是在跟军队作战
you're not fighting an army.
你得把它想成是一个单独的生物体
You have to think of this as a single organism.
看 这些触手让它们行动非常灵活
Now, these common drones, they act like its claws.
阿尔法
And Alphas,
就是你杀死的那种 数量没那么多
like the one that you killed, are much more rare.
- 没错 我估计618万才会有一只 - 是的
Yeah. They're like one in 6.18 million, by my guess. - Yes.
它们会预知敌人的行动
They act as the enemy's...
就像中枢神经系统一样
They're like its central nervous system.
而这个
But this...
就是大脑
is the brain.
它们的指挥部
It controls them all.
它就是欧米伽
And this is the Omega.
它有一种控制时间的能力
And the Omega has the ability to control time.
一旦阿尔法被杀
Whenever an Alpha is killed...
一种自动反应就会被触发
an automatic response is triggered.
指挥部这儿 就会重启当天
The Omega starts the day over again.
你一定要知道
But you see, this time,
它会记住即将发生的事
it can remember what's going to happen
就像你一样
just like you do.
在我们行动之前 它会预知我们要干什么
It knows exactly what we're gonna do before we're gonna do it.
能预知未来的敌人
And an enemy that knows the future can't lose.
很难战胜
It can't lose.
如果真这样 凡尔登是怎么赢的
But if that's true, how did you win at Verdun?
是对方故意的
We were allowed to win.
它想让我们相信 我们能赢
This thing wants us to believe we can win.
诱使我们不惜一切代价投入这场战争
It wants us to throw everything we have into the invasion.
其实这场战争 不是我们的收官之战
Operation Downfall isn't our endgame
而是敌人的
it's the enemy's.
你要明白
The thing you've got to understand is
这是一种 经过完美进化的霸主级生物
this is a perfectly evolved world-conquering organism.
可以想象 会有成千上万的这样的东西
For all we know, there are millions of those asteroids...
漂浮在宇宙中 就像病毒一样
floating around in the cosmos like a virus.
它们就等着在合适的条件下登陆地球
They're just waiting to crash-land into a world with just the right conditions.
最终目的 是攻击地球上的人类 然后
All they need is for the dominant life form to attack and:
它们会横扫一切 统治整个地球
There'll be nothing to stop the mimics from conquering the rest of the world.
只有你才能阻挡它们
Unless you change the outcome.
我
Me?
你杀掉阿尔法的时候
When you killed that Alpha, you inadvertently
无意中进入了敌人的神经系统
entered the enemy's nervous system.
凯奇
Cage,
你掌握了它控制时间的能力 可以随时重启当天
you've seized control of the Omega's ability to reset the day.
这怎么可能
How's that even possible?
这东西唯一的弱点
Perhaps this organism's only vulnerability,
和对付它最有效的手段
its only vulnerability...
就是人性
is humanity.
不管怎么样 你拥有了这个能力
Regardless of that, you control the power now.
就像当初我在凡尔登时一样
Just as I did in Verdun.
所以我能重启时间
So I'm resetting the day?
好吧
Okay.
需要怎么做
How do I control it?
你必须得死
You have to die.
天天死
Every day.
直到这东西被摧毁
Until the Omega's destroyed.
首先
First of all...
你的演示很精彩
this is a terrific presentation.
非常完美
Terrific.
我认识将军
I know the general.
我们应该向他汇报
We should take this to him.
告诉将军你们说的这一切
You just tell him everything you told me.
我去见过将军 凯奇
I went to see the general, Cage.
而且是无数次
Any number of times.
精神病院 解剖研究 记得吗
Psych ward. Dissection. Remember?
那你们希望我怎么做
What are you expecting from me?
你有没有看到什么异象
Have you seen anything strange?
开玩笑吗
Is he shitting me?
是幻象
Visions.
幻象 你看见过这样的幻象吗
Visions. Have you seen any visions like that?
它对力量失去控制会有感知
The Omega senses when it's losing control of its power.
现在 它一直在用精神力量搜寻你
Even now it's mentally searching to find you.
一旦你快被找到时 就会产生各种幻象
When it's close to finding you you will start having visions.
你就会看见它
You'll start to see that.
甚至能看到它在哪儿
You'll even see where it is.
你也看过幻象
And you had these visions?
是的
Yes.
你亲眼见过它 我是说 真正的看
But eventually you saw it. I mean, you actually saw it.
对吗
Right?
我从没见过它
Never in the flesh.
那这一切都只是
So this is all just some...
理论
theory.
你无法确定这东西
You don't know if this thing even exists.
幻象告诉我 它就在凡尔登
The visions showed me it was at Verdun.
我都看见了 我
I could see it. I...
我只是
I just...
在找到它之前失去了这种能力
lost the power before I could get to it.
等我们拿下凡尔登
And by the time we took Verdun...
那家伙早跑了
the Omega was gone.
好吧 那我要做的就是等待这些幻象
Okay. So all I have to do is wait to have these visions...
然后 再告诉你们这家伙在哪儿
and then tell you where this Omega thing is.
不 凯奇
No. Cage.
你要带我去那儿
You're gonna get me there.
由我来干掉它
And I'm gonna kill it.
带你去
Get you there?
我根本没接受过战斗训练
I'm not even trained for combat.
【 重新装弹 】
重新装弹
Reload.
没事吧 凯奇
Are you all right, Cage?
好像哪儿摔断了
I think I broke something.
哪儿
What?
我的背
My back.
我现在只能感觉到嘴唇
The only thing I can feel are my lips.
你仔细听好了 这是条很重要的规则
Now listen carefully. This is a very important rule.
也是唯一的规则
This is the only rule.
如果在战斗中受伤 你要保证自己死去
You get injured on the field, you better make sure you die.
为什么
Why?
上次我在战斗中 被击中了
Last time I was in combat... I was hit.
当时失血很多 差点儿就死了
I was bleeding out. Just not fast enough.
输了三品托血后 我在战地医院苏醒过来
I woke up in a field hospital with three pints of someone else's blood
人已经废了
and I was out.
失去了那种能力 你明白吗
I lost the power. Do you understand?
再来一遍吧 你觉得呢
Think we better start over. Don't you?
什么
What?
没人知道二等兵凯奇怎么了吗
No one knows what happened to Private Cage!
斯金纳 你这笨蛋 他就在你旁边
You dumb-ass. He was right next to you.
别告诉我你不知道那家伙跑哪儿去了
You don't know where that slippery son of a bitch went?
不 中士
No, sarge!
好吧
All right.
那就再来50个 怎么样
Let's do another 50, shall we?
一
And one!
不 等等 我叫威廉姆·凯奇
No, wait! Wait. My name is Bill Cage.
我们在海滩见过
I... We met on the beach.
是将在海滩见 明天
We meet on the beach. Tomorrow.
我们是一类人
I have what you had.
好了 再来一遍
Ugh. All right, let's go again.
你没有时间多想
You don't have time to think.
要记住 光知道它们的位置还不够
Remember. It's not enough knowing where they're going to be.
必须知道怎么杀掉它们
You have to know how to kill them.
等等 等等 听着
Hold on. Hold on. Listen. List...
好吧 动手吧
Okay. Do it.
站起来 废物
On your feet, maggot!
停 等等 等等 等等
Stop! Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
停下来 等 等一下
Stop! Wait! Wait a second!
等一下
Wait a second.
我一直在想
You know, I've been thinking.
听着 我血液里的东西
I mean, this thing's in my blood.
也许有什么办法 我可以把它传给你
So maybe there's some way I can transfer it to you.
我试过了 根本不行
I've tried everything. It doesn't work.
你有没有试过
I mean, have you...
你知道的
you know...
试过所有的可能性
tried all the options?
你是说性行为 对 试过了
Oh, you mean sex. Yep. Tried it.
试过几次
How many times?
行了
All right.
左边
Left.
左边 左边 左边
Left! Left, left!
睁大你的眼睛
Keep your eyes open.
再来
Again.
等等 等等
Just wait! Wait.
我觉得可以了
I think I'm okay.
站起来 废物
On your feet Maggot!
废物
Maggot!
我已经很客气了 废物 快动起来
I'm trying to be nice to you, maggot! Move!
你没事吧 凯奇
You okay, Cage?
没事 我很好
Oh yeah, yeah! I'm good! I'm good!
你的腿断了
Your leg's broken.
没有 我还能感觉到脚趾
No. I can still feel my toes.
噢 不是吧
Oh, come on.
警告 危险
瑞塔 这什么意思
Rita. Rita. What is this?
你来这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
- 他是谁 - 他就是我
- Who's this guy? - He's me...
- 凡尔登之前的 - 凡尔登之前的
- ...before Verdun. - Before Verdun.
什么 你是说他是
What do you mean? He's...?
对
Yes. Yes.
什么时候死的
When did he die?
- 在哪儿 - 在海滩 明天
- Where? - On the beach. Tomorrow.
我是威廉姆·凯奇 你是卡特博士
I'm Bill Cage. You're Dr. Carter.
我们曾有这次对话 你在背后竖起两根手指
We've had this conversation before. Two fingers behind your back.
我看到幻象
I've had the visions.
见到那东西了
I've seen the Omega.
我们 明天会败得很惨
It's pretty much game over tomorrow.
所以 不必浪费时间了
So can we move this along?
好吧 在哪儿
Okay. Where?
那儿有水坝
There's a dam.
在山里 我看见了德文标识
It's in the mountains. I saw German writing.
你能找到它的位置吗
Do you think you can work out where that is?
我觉得你说的那种地方不会太多
I mean, there can't be too many places that fit that description.
我来试试吧
I'll see what I can do.
训练结束了 我们明天见
Training's over. I'll see you tomorrow.
我们还不知道去哪儿
We don't even know where we're going.
很快就会知道了
We will soon enough.
你现在要想想 怎么在海滩上保住命
In the meantime, you need to figure out a way to get us off that beach.
然后呢 我们去哪儿
What next? Where are we going?
哪条路 快想 哪条路
Which way? Focus. Which way?
- 我在想 我在想 - 好吧
- I'm thinking. - Okay.
该死
Oh, man!
我们走了多远
How far did we make it?
要知道 这真的很难说
You know, it's hard to say, really.
等等 等等
Hold! Hold!
好了 走
Okay, go!
这狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
我想往左走 躲开 说清楚点儿
I thought stepping left, ducking... Just for the record.
- 往左挪步 往右躲避 - 已经很具体了
- Stepping left, ducking right. - It was pretty specific.
往左挪步 往右躲避
Stepping left, ducking right.
继续
Move on.
等等
Hold on!
现在记住 要穿过战壕 正前方
Across the trench, 12:00!
注意你的右侧
Then look to your right!
还是不够具体 明白吗
You're not being specific.
必须要非常具体 否则我死定了
You need to be specific. Otherwise, I'm dead.
瑞塔
Rita.
凯奇
Cage!
一步一步走到战壕的顶端 向左挪步
Paces up to the top of the trench. I'm gonna step left.
那儿有敌人 我会杀掉它
A mimic there, which I'll kill.
飞船爆炸 我要向西北前进30步
Ship explosion. I'm gonna run 30 paces northwest.
到达战壕顶端时要蹲下
I'm gonna duck at the top of that trench
然后应该向左转
and then I'm gonna turn left.
我脸上长花了吗
Have I got something on my face?
没有
No.
凯奇
Cage!
我们在到处找你
We've been looking everywhere for you.
凯奇
Cage!
凯奇 我们在到处
Cage, we've been looking...
伙计们
Guys.
伙计们 等等
Guys. Can we...
今天
just...
就歇一歇吧
not do this today?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
因为找不到你 法莱尔都快把我们折磨死了
Farell almost strung us up by our bollocks for losing track of you.
好了 斯金纳 你看着
Okay, Skinner. Watch this.
现在我闭上眼睛
Now I'm gonna close my eyes.
- 好了 - 嗯
- Ready? - Yeah.
该死的 混蛋
Sneaky bastard.
我一点儿都没埋怨你
I didn't mind the extra push-ups.
早上好 伙计们
It's a new day people.
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
这世界只要我们做一件事 取得胜利
The world expects only one thing from us: That we will win.
从前线传回的战况
Current situation on the front line.
联合防御部队伤亡惨重
Our troops have suffered heavy casualties.
是时候让那些东西看看我们的实力了
It's about time we showed those things what we're made of.
我父亲可是不列颠之战中的飞行员
My father flew in the Battle of Britain.
美国人是三年后才参战的
Three years before the Yanks came into the war.
我们势不可挡 绝对有种
Couldn't be broken. Backbone.
我叔叔乔治参加过诺曼底登陆
My Uncle George landed on the beach at Normandy.
真的
Yeah?
让他们打 这仗我们早就拿下了
In their day, this war would have been over by now.
这些家伙到底想要什么
What do they want with us, anyway?
这还用问吗 矿产
It's obvious, isn't it? Minerals.
- 矿产 - 对 金属矿产
- Minerals? - Yeah, minerals. Metals.
- 它们要的是氧气 - 氧气
- Oxygen, they want. - Oxygen?
- 想想吧 - 这有什么区别
- Think about it. - What difference does it make?
它们来了 也赢了
They're here. They're winning.
无论想要什么 都会得到的
And whatever it is, they're gonna get it.
你不是该去那儿吗
Shouldn't you be over there?
我早去过了
I've been over there.
比谁去的次数都多
More times than anybody.
不怕告诉你们
As a matter of fact,
我已经死过很多次了
I'm usually long dead by now.
胆小鬼
Coward.
怎么回事
What's going on?
停电了
The power's gone.
我找到欧米伽了
I found the Omega.
它一定在这儿 德国卡内拉大坝 肯定是这儿
I found it. It has to be here. Curnera Dam, Germany.
跟描述完全一致
This has got to be it. It fits the description.
是的 你找到了
You found it.
又一次
Again.
那又能怎么样
What difference does it make?
我们根本到不了那儿
Because we're never gonna get there.
不管我们怎么做
No matter what we do...
不管我们怎么精心策划
no matter how carefully we plan...
都过不了海滩那一关
we can't get off that beach.
你能做到的 你能
You can do this. You can.
你每天都到这儿来 我来训练你
You keep coming here every day and I'll train you.
已经训练过了
You already have.
什么情况 南希
I'm waiting, Nance!
500米外 正在迅速逼近
Five hundred meters and closing fast!
怎么回事
What the...?
重新装弹
Reload.
下面怎么做
What's next?
一直向前 到山那儿
Straight shot up the hill.
好
Okay.
中士 新来那家伙
Hey, sarge, the new guy...
他叫什么来着
what's his name again?
得有交通工具才能深入到内陆
We'll need a vehicle to get further inland.
有什么问题吗
What's the problem?
问题是那里肯定有伏击 还没找到车就会被杀掉
The ambush waiting for us. They kill us before we find a working car.
好吧 那眼下怎么办
Okay. So, what's the current plan?
还有两辆车可以试试 小型货车
Two cars we haven't tried yet.
- 和绿色越野车 - 好的
- The minivan and the green SUV. - Yeah. Okay.
我去找越野车 把模仿者引过去
I'll head for the SUV, draw the mimics to me. You go for the minivan.
你去找小型货车 发动之后就直接开走 不用等我
You get it started, just go, take off. Do not wait for me.
好的
Okay.
对了 发动前一定别忘了把拖车解开
Just don't forget to disconnect the caravan before you take off.
你要的是速度 别拖着个累赘
You are going to be in a hurry, you don't want any dead weight.
拜托
Come on.
快呀 凯奇
Come on, Cage!
敌人已经攻陷了多佛
The enemy has breached security at Dover.
我看不见
Can't see.
你能吗
Can you?
政府提醒市民不要外出 保持镇定
Stay where you are and remain calm.
如果你在车里
If you are in a vehicle
请锁上车 不要出来
please lock doors and stay inside.
对不起 敌人已经到了伦敦
I'm sorry. The enemy has reached London.
国际广播
重复一遍
Repeat:
伦敦也受到了袭击
London is under attack.
车技不错
Good driving.
我忘了解开拖车
I forgot to unhook the trailer.
启动
Engage.
【 启 动 】
你不太爱说话
You don't talk much.
不喜欢说话
I'm not a fan.
说话
Of talking?
不太喜欢说话 对
Not a fan of talking. No.
不过 你还是跟我说了
You know you eventually do talk to me.
你曾经跟我说过 你和家人一起去过里昂
It's usually around Lyons. You tell me about the time you went there with your family.
你弟弟走丢了
Your brother got lost.
我从没去过里昂
I've never been to Lyons.
还说过你的中间名
You tell me your middle name.
佩顿
Peyton.
那不是我的中间名
That's not my middle name.
你是在拱廊找到你弟弟的
You find your brother in the arcade, by the way.
那都是我胡编的 为了让你安静点儿
Well, maybe I made it all up just to keep you quiet.
反正我们聊过
But you do talk to me.
凯奇 我没有必要去了解你
Cage, I do not need to get to know you.
如果你是聪明人 就别跟我套近乎
If you knew what was good for you, you wouldn't want to get to know me.
多想想怎么保命吧
It's the only way you make it through this thing.
那你了解汉德里克吗
What about Hendricks? You get to know him?
你怎么知道这个名字
How do you know that name?
你说的
You mentioned him.
这根本不可能
That's not possible.
不然我怎么知道
Then how do I know his name?
我什么时候说的 是在什么情况下
When did I mention him? Under what circumstance?
因为他 你才不跟我说话
Is he why you won't talk to me?
你最好别再提他的名字
Don't ever mention his name again.
为什么
Why?
- 你爱他 - 他死了
Are you... in love with him? - He's dead.
我亲眼看他死过300次
And I watched him die 300 times
而且记得
and I remember...
所有细节
every detail.
记得所有的一切
I remember everything.
所以我不想再谈这些
So I don't need to talk about it.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
战争就是这样
It's just war.
油量低
什么都没有 我们走吧
There's nothing here. Let's keep going.
得先找到钥匙
We have to find the keys.
弄点儿油就行了
Let's just siphon the gas.
有飞机为什么还要开车
Why drive when we can fly?
这东西
In that thing?
我知道了 你肯定恐高
Let me guess. You're afraid of heights.
我是害怕坠机
I'm afraid of crashing.
这又没什么可丢人的
And not at all ashamed to admit it.
没事的 凯奇 能克服
You'll be fine, Cage. You'll learn. Oh.
怎么了
What is it?
没什么 我没事
It's nothing. I'm fine.
- 怎么了 - 没什么
- What is it? - It's nothing.
瑞塔
Rita.
我看看
Let me see.
得找到直升机的钥匙
We have to find the keys to the helicopter.
肯定在附近什么地方
I'm sure they're around here somewhere.
直升机的油是满的
You know, the heli's full of fuel, though.
我找到一根软管
I found a hose.
开飞机 凯奇
We're flying, Cage.
你知道就算我们找到了钥匙
Let's just say we find the keys. You know?
就算开走了那架直升机
Get that helicopter started.
我们既没有战甲 也没有弹药
We don't have our jackets or ammunition.
马上就要天黑了
It's gonna be dark in a few hours.
我们还不如回到刚才那个农舍
Might be better off just going back to the farmhouse.
找点什么有用的
Seeing what we could salvage.
在那里过一夜 早上再回这儿
Spend the night there. Come back here in the morning.
蜷缩在篝火旁边 再开上一瓶好酒
And curl up by the fire and open a bottle of wine.
我觉得我们还是应该重置
I think we should just reset.
这是死路一条 对你来说都一样
It's a dead end. If it's all the same to you
可我累了 很痛苦
I'm tired. I'm in pain.
- 我宁可重新再来一次 - 听我说
- I'd rather just start fresh. - Tell you what.
先休息一下
Take a few minutes.
咖啡煮好了
Coffee's ready.
我去找找钥匙 应该能找到
I'll look for the keys. That's productive.
- 10分钟 - 好吧
- Ten minutes. - Okay.
然后我杀掉你
Then I'm killing you.
好啊
Fine.
你居然能找到咖啡
I can't believe you found coffee.
谢谢
Thank you.
加糖 对吗
Sugar, right?
对
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
等等 三勺 要加三勺
No, hold on. Three. You like three.
那儿有件衬衣 你应该能穿
There's a shirt over there. It should be your size.
我们来这里几次了
How many times have we been here?
来过几次
How many times?
钥匙在哪儿
Where are the keys?
- 钥匙到底在哪儿 - 好吧
- Where are the goddamn keys? - Okay.
你会开的 对吗
You can fly it, can't you?
不会 会
No. Well, yes.
我是说 我只会起飞 降落还没学会
I mean, I can take off. I'm still working on my landing.
那还在这里干什么 简直在浪费时间
What are we still doing here? You're wasting time!
瑞塔 发动引擎你就会死
Rita, if you start that engine, you die.
永远回不去了
This is as far as you go.
无论我做什么
No matter what I do...
你都会永远死在这里
this is as far as you ever make it.
20码以外藏着一个模仿者外星人
There's a mimic buried 20 yards away.
你发动引擎 它就会攻击你
It attacks when you start the engine.
拿上你的武器上直升机 凯奇
Get your weapon and get in the helicopter, Cage.
回到那边会遇到更多
There's more in the field back there.
我们俩只有一个能回去
Only one of us ever makes it.
上来
Get in.
唯一没有试过的方案就是
Only thing we haven't tried is
你让开 回到农舍去
you walk away. Go to the farmhouse.
那里有地窖 有吃的
There's a cellar and there's food.
你在这儿等着我回来 你会安全的
Wait there till I get back. You'll be safe.
我是战士
I'm a soldier.
是我自愿的 我不会让开
I volunteered. I'm not walking away.
那你会死的 死在这儿
You die here. Right here.
我救不了你
I can't save you.
如果我去杀了那东西 你会死的
And if I go on and kill the Omega, you're dead.
是真死
Forever.
我怎么样有那么重要吗
Why does it matter what happens to me?
我希望 没见过你
I wish... I didn't know you.
可是不行
But I do.
我的中间名
My middle name...
是罗斯
is Rose.
站起来 废物
On your feet, maggot!
好消息是你还有希望 二等兵
The good news is there's hope for you, private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
也是一个大熔炉 能锤炼出真正的英雄
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
什么事
Yes?
谁让你跟我说话了
Who said you could talk to me?
难道我脸花了吗 士兵
Have I got something on my face, soldier?
很抱歉 打扰你了
I'm sorry to disturb you, sergeant.
好了 伙计 开始了 我得穿得正式点儿
Let's get this show on the road. I gotta suit up.
你的头盔呢
Where's your helmet?
从来没带过 很烦人的
Never wear one. It's a distraction.
你喝酒了吧
Have you been drinking?
再给我三个5.56的弹簧夹
I need three more clips of 5.56...
八颗手雷 还有一块电池
eight grenades and an extra battery.
快点儿
Get it.
嗨
Oi!
伙计
Oi, mate!
你的衣服好像不太对劲儿
There's something wrong with your suit.
里面装的是死人
There's a dead guy in it.
我们成功了
We made it!
感谢上帝 我们成功了
Thank God, we made it!
警告 危险
来杀我呀
Finish it!
它不在那儿
It isn't there.
你什么意思 欧米伽不在那儿
What do you mean? Omega  isn't there.
我猜它从来就没在那儿
My guess is it never was.
它们知道我们要来 它们伏击了我们
They knew we were coming. They ambushed us.
幻象就是个陷阱
The visions were a trap.
就像瑞塔在凡尔登看到的幻象一样
Just like Rita's visions were a trap at Verdun.
它可以杀我但没杀
It could have killed me, but it didn't.
它想要我的血
It was after my blood.
那它们知道你是谁了
So they know who you are. They...
它们想恢复能力
They want their power back.
就算这次没成 早晚也会
They're gonna get it one way or another.
除非我们能找到欧米伽
Unless we find the Omega.
没别的办法了 我们完了
There isn't any other way. We're finished.
不
No.
我们还没完
We're not finished.
那个没用 我无法让它工作
I can't get it to work.
你在白厅做过一个原型
You built a prototype at Whitehall.
没错 托你的福 我为此丢了工作
Yes, and I got fired for it, thank you very much.
- 这到底是什么东西 - 这是个转发器
- What is this thing? - It's a transponder.
把它放到阿尔法体内
Stick it into the Alpha
它会跟欧米伽之间产生信息波段
and it taps into the wavelength connecting it to the Omega.
这就是它的工作原理
That's the idea, anyway.
但我没法让它工作 现有的设备根本不行
I can't get it to work. Not with the equipment I have.
哪儿有你需要的设备
How do we get what you need?
刚才她不是说了吗 在白厅里的那个
That's the thing. When I was at Whitehall, I built one.
差不多都可以进行测试了
I was even ready to test it.
我跟主管汇报以后 就把工作丢了
When I told my superiors about it, I lost my job.
都觉得他疯了
They thought he was crazy.
所以我们需要去趟白厅
So we need to go to Whitehall.
没等接近大门 你就会被捕的
She'd be arrested 10 feet from the front door.
精神病院 解剖试验 记得吗
Psych ward, dissection, remember?
嗨 嗨 嗨
Hey, hey, hey.
你们还忘了一件事
Aren't you forgetting something?
转发器要在活的阿尔法身上才管用
The transponder requires a live Alpha to make it work.
我们不需要
We don't need one.
我们有更好的选择
We got the next best thing.
等中国代表团出来时 要加快脚步
When the Chinese delegation comes out we pick up the pace.
那个戴黄袖章的家伙每次都能认出你
This guy with the yellow armband always recognizes you...
所以你要低着头 在我右边走
so just keep your head down and stay to my right.
干得不错
Nicely done.
三 二 一 走
Three, two, one. Go.
一
One...
六 七 八
Six, seven, eight...
十二
Twelve...
十五
Fifteen. Now.
然后
And,
转身
turn.
好的 继续走 眼睛往前看
Okay. Keep walking. Just stare straight ahead.
罗宾森
Robinson.
我说过了 别打扰我 你最好有个好理由
I've asked not to be disturbed. This had better be critical.
人类的生死存亡
The fate of mankind.
这个理由够吗
Critical enough?
我不是活见鬼了吧
I don't believe what I'm seeing.
我已经见过很多次了
I've had more than my share of that.
坐下 将军 离那桌子远一点
Sit down, general. Stay away from the desk.
我要是你 就不会当儿戏
I'd take her very seriously if I were you.
真是让人佩服 少校
Have to hand it to you, major.
你离开这间办公室的时候 就没想到你会回来
When you left this office today, I never imagined you'd be back...
更别说是载誉归来的战斗英雄
let alone with my most decorated soldier.
我给你讲个故事吧 将军
I'm gonna tell you a story. general.
一开始听着肯定会觉得很荒唐
It's gonna sound ridiculous.
但你越往下听 会越觉得合理
The longer I talk, the more rational it's going to appear.
告诉他 一会儿打回去
Tell him you'll call back.
告诉谁
Tell who?
是博蒙特少校 从哈利法克斯打来的
Major General Beaumont, calling from Halifax.
他的飞机没能按时起飞 天气不好
His plane's just been delayed. Bad weather.
你好
Yes.
谢谢 博蒙特 一会儿打给你
Thank you, Beaumont. I'll call you back.
明天的战斗是场屠杀
Tomorrow's invasion is a slaughter.
我到海滩上 不超过5分钟就会死
I'm dead within minutes of landing along
那些被你送上去的士兵也一样
with every other soldier you are sending.
因为敌人早就知道我们的计划
And that's because the enemy knows we're coming.
我怎么知道的
How do I know this?
我临死前
Before I died...
杀了一个外星人 只是它有点儿特别
I killed a mimic, only this one was different.
它传了一些东西到我的血液里
It passed something on to me. In my blood.
我能在同一天里周而复始地活着
Now I live the same day over and over again.
跟它们一样
Just like they do.
沃塔斯基中士在凡尔登也一样
Just like Sergeant Vrataski at Verdun.
告诉你的秘书 你这儿一切正常
Tell your secretary everything's fine.
你说什么
Beg your pardon?
我很抱歉 将军 不知道您有客人
Sorry, general. I thought you were alone.
没事
It's fine.
她打印好了文件等你签字
She typed up those orders for you to authorize.
但忘了格林威治燃油丢弃计划那部分
But she left out the ones referring to the fuel dump at Greenwich.
你叫艾丽丝
Your name is Iris.
你的生日是9月17号
Your birthday is September 17th.
将军私下动用了一些关系
The general pulled some strings...
把你的独生子安排到了澳大利亚 以远离战争
stationed your son in Australia, as far from the war as possible.
你刚接到电话 将军的晚餐预约取消了
Tell the general his dinner's been canceled. The call came in just now.
晚餐预约取消了
Your dinner was canceled.
你忘了燃油部分
You forgot the fuel dump.
谢谢你 艾丽丝 出去吧
Thank you, Iris. That'll be all.
- 凯奇 动手吧 - 瑞塔
- Cage, let's go. - Rita.
- 我们应该 别再向他开枪了 - 我们还等什么
- Let me... Don't shoot him again. - What are we doing?
好吗 我们应该
Okay? Just...
将军
General,
这场对话我们不是第一次进行
this isn't the first time we've had this conversation.
就因为你
That's because you're...
非常固执
stubborn.
你不相信我告诉你的 卡特博士是正确的
You won't believe me when I tell you that Dr. Carter was right.
敌人可以随意控制时间
That the enemy can manipulate time.
我们注定失败
The invasion will fail.
无论你让多少战士去送死
No matter how many bodies you throw at it.
赢得这场战争的唯一办法就是
The only way to win this war is...
找到模仿者的核心能量 消灭它
by finding this power source of the mimic horde and killing it.
而找到这种能量的关键 就在那个保险箱里
And the only means of finding it is in that safe right there.
无论这场谈话我们进行多少次
No matter how many times we have this conversation...
你都不相信 明天敌人就会攻陷伦敦
you refuse to accept that the enemy breaks through to London tomorrow...
我们会失败 败得干净彻底
and we lose. We lose everything.
就算真是这样
Let's say for one moment...
又怎么合理地解释
that I can't rationally explain...
你这金口玉牙的本事
your impressive parlor tricks.
卡特博士说过
Dr. Carter told me...
需要活着的外星人它才能起作用
this device requires a live mimic to work.
你要它有什么用
What use is it to you?
- 这是我的问题 - 正好相反
- That's my concern. - On the contrary.
按你说的 这事关系到全世界
According to you, this concerns the whole world.
那你会怎么做 如果你相信我刚才说的话
Well, what would you do if you believed everything I just told you?
- 我会找到那个 - 欧米伽
- I would locate this... - Omega.
把它炸得粉身碎骨
Bomb it out of existence.
用这种思维模式跟它斗
You're not mentally equipped to fight this thing.
永远赢不了
And you never will be.
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
不知道 还没到过这一步
I don't know. We've never gotten this far.
挺容易的
That was easy.
站住
Down!
- 站住 - 不许动
- Stop right there! - Don't move!
都不许动
Nobody move!
有武器
Weapon!
停车
Stop!
- 他们跑了 - 他们跑了
- They're off and away! - They're...
这东西怎么用
What am I supposed to do with this?
插进你的大腿
Stick it in your leg.
快
Do it!
凯奇 感受到了什么
Cage, what's happening?
告诉我
Talk to me.
我感觉到它了 我正在往那儿去
I feel it. It's taking me there.
你看见什么了
What do you see?
是罗浮宫
It's the Louvre.
哪儿 你在哪儿
Where? Where are you?
我在罗浮宫里 好多的水
I'm inside now. It's flooded.
再往下去有个车库 博物馆地下的车库
Now I'm going down. I'm in a garage. A garage underneath the museum.
能看见欧米伽吗
The Omega. Can you see it?
它在巴黎
It's in Paris.
瑞塔
Rita!
待在车里
Stay in the car!
- 退后 - 让开 让开
- Stay back. - Move away. Move away.
你在干什么
What have you done?
怎么会这样
你没事的 只是需要输血
You'll be fine. You just needed blood.
你不知道你在干什么
You don't know what you've just done.
我不能跟你闲聊
I can't talk to you.
跟我一起的
I was with someone.
瑞塔·沃塔斯基 还活着吗
Rita Vrataski. Is she alive?
瑞塔·沃塔斯基
Rita Vrataski.
求你了
Please.
快告诉我
Just tell me that.
求你告诉我
Please tell me.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我解开这东西最多用不了3分钟
I was out of those things in three minutes flat.
凯奇 你怎么了
Cage, What's wrong with you?
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
还没死
Not yet.
- 抱歉 凯奇 - 不 等等
- Sorry, Cage. - No! Whoa. Wait! Wait!
我完了 结束了 我被输了血
I'm out. I'm out. They gave me blood.
失去那能力了
I lost the power.
能感觉到
I feel it.
我无法再重置时间了
I can't reset the day anymore.
得赶在开战之前 想法杀掉欧米伽
We have to kill the Omega before the invasion starts.
剩下不到三个小时了
That gives us less than three hours.
想及时赶到巴黎 需要一艘飞船
We need a drop ship to get to Paris in time.
还需要更多的战士
Need more soldiers too.
谁会疯狂到跟我们去巴黎
Now, who's crazy enough to follow us to Paris?
凯奇
Cage!
- 伙计们 - 我们都在到处找你
- Guys! - We've been looking everywhere for you.
你们听我说
Just listen.
- 因为找不到你 法莱尔都快把我们折磨死了 - 我知道
- Farell almost strung us up or losing track of you. - I know.
好了 听着
Just listen.
听我给你们讲个故事
You're gonna wanna hear this.
一开始听着肯定会觉得很荒唐
It's gonna sound ridiculous at first.
但是往下听 就会越来越觉得合理
The longer I talk, the more rational it's going to appear.
是吗
Yeah?
知道我学校的名字
He named the school I went to.
还说出了我二年级老师的名字 叫拐子小姐
And then he tells me my second grade teacher was called Miss Polio.
她不让他去厕所 害得他尿了裤子
She wouldn't let him go to the bathroom made him wet his pants.
你闭嘴
Shut up.
听着 我就是告诉你们
Look, I am telling you, man.
他什么事都知道
He knows everything.
我们所有的事
About all of us.
- 别扯了 - 不信
- Bullshit. - Yeah?
他还说 你的名字不是福特
He says your name ain't really Ford.
福特其实是你的朋友
Says Ford was your friend.
在参战的第一天就阵亡了
Died in combat on his first day.
你代替了他 还给他家里人寄钱
You took his place. Send your checks to his family.
潜伏得可够深的
You slippery bitch.
凯奇说敌人知道我们的计划
Cage says the enemy knows us too.
正在海滩等我们
They're waiting for us on the beach.
我们都会死
And we all die.
那根本就是一场屠杀
The whole invasion is a slaughter.
真是好极了
Well, this is great.
战前动员做得不错 谢了 伙计
Really good confidence boost for tomorrow. Thanks. Guys.
我们还有机会 对吗
But we can change it, right?
我们肯定能做点什么
There has to be something that we can do.
总会有取胜的办法的
There has to be a way that we can win.
是有个机会 但很渺茫
There is a chance. It's a slim one.
需要你们跟我走 马上
But it means coming with me right now.
听着 伙计
Listen, pal.
我不管你知道多少我们的私事
I don't really care what you think you know about us.
我们刚认识你
We just met you.
凭什么让我们跟着你去打仗
Why follow him into combat?
没指望你们跟我走
I don't expect you to follow me.
你们可以跟她走
I expect you to follow her.
- 这不是全金属贱人吗 - 伙计们
- That's the Full Metal Bitch. - J Squad.
她是瑞塔·沃塔斯基
This is Rita Vrataski.
- 大家都叫她 - 对
- Otherwise known as... - Yeah, yeah.
凡尔登的天使
The Angel of Verdun.
好吧
Okay.
早上好
It's a new day, people.
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
这世界只要我们做一件事 取得胜利
The world expects only one thing from us: That we will win.
如果你们今天不全力拚搏 最高兴的肯定是敌人
Rest assured the enemy will thank you for not giving 100 percent today.
全体注意
Squad?
J小队去哪儿了
Where's J Squad?
好了 听着
Right, okay.
这个欧米伽 能随意控制时间
So this Omega, it controls time.
把这帮新世代的混蛋炸回老家
Just blow the New Age bollocks back where it came from.
就都结束了
And then we go home.
对 但它还有阿尔法保护着
Right, it's guarded by an Alpha.
连它一起杀 明白
Just kill it. Okay?
不
No!
你们没听凯奇说吗
You heard what Cage said.
不能杀掉阿尔法
Do not kill an Alpha.
杀掉阿尔法 欧米伽会把一整天重置一遍
If we do, the Omega will reset this whole day.
我们都不会记得这次谈话
We'll never remember we had this conversation.
它们却知道我们
They're gonna know we're coming.
如果遇到阿尔法要杀我 那我该怎么做
What am I supposed to do if an Alpha is about to kill me?
为全队牺牲自己
You take a hit for the team.
我们空降之后
When we're on the ground...
它们很快就会知道我们到了 我们没多少时间
there's not gonna be a lot of time before they know we're there.
要设置一个观察哨
We're gonna need eyes up here.
我也参加 凯奇
I'm going in, Cage.
还有30秒到达
Thirty seconds till contact.
凯奇
Cage!
基梅尔 不
Kimmel! No!
福特
Ford!
快走
Let's go!
凯奇
Cage!
我们该走了
Talk to me, Rita! We gotta go.
跳
Drop.
凯奇 它们知道我们要来
Cage, they know we're coming, man!
跳 跳
Drop! Drop!
跳
Drop!
Drop.
得挂上 弹出去
You're not hooked in.
弹 出
你怎么那么慢
What took you so long?
还有活着的吗
Any others?
我们快没弹药了
We're low on ammo.
我还有双刃砍刀 福特 你没弹药了
I've got one Claymore. Ford, you're out.
格瑞夫的弹药库只剩一半子弹了 他动弹不了了
Griff has only got half a magazine and he can hardly move.
你不是能看到未来吗
I thought you could see the future.
我刚来到今天
I haven't lived this day.
不知道会发生什么
I don't know what's gonna happen.
别纠结了
It doesn't matter.
想想怎么干掉它们
What matters is we finish this.
怎么干
With What?
我是说 格瑞夫不能动了
I mean, Griff can't even walk.
我们死了三个人 算了吧
We're three men down. Come on.
听着 别浪费时间了 集中弹药
We're running out of time. Collect your ammo.
我们和金字塔之间有上千个外星人
Must be a thousand mimics between us and the pyramid.
你说怎么做 难道直接走正门吗
What we gonna do? Walk up to the front door?
- 不能待在这儿等死 - 是吗
- If we stay here, we die. - Yeah?
肯定过不去的
We'll never get through.
能过去
We could.
用那个
In that.
那东西飞不起来
That ship will never fly.
不用飞起来
Doesn't need to fly.
只要能带着我们快速穿过那里 就够了
It just needs to get us across there with speed.
如果引擎还能启动 用动力杆操控就行
If the engines are still running, we could steer it with the power levers.
斯金纳 清理通道
Skinner. Clear a path.
- 现在再试一次 - 不 还没反应
- Try it again, now. - No, it's not reading.
状态控制杆 拉低
Condition lever, low.
主电源 打开
Master power, on.
格瑞夫
Griff!
我们要走了 快点儿
We've gotta go! Come on!
我帮不上什么忙了
I'm not gonna be any good in there, mate.
让我给你们争取点时间吧
Let me buy you some time.
易燃品
电源启动了
Power's on.
会成功的
This is gonna work.
嗨
Hey!
快点儿 伙计 我们要走了
Hey, come on, man! We gotta go!
别等我们了
Don't wait for us!
斯金纳 格瑞夫 快点儿
Skinner! Griff, come on!
可以出发了 他们呢
We're good to go. Where are they?
斯金纳和格瑞夫呢
Where's Skinner and Griff?
他们不来了
They're not coming.
走 老兄 你必须走 老兄
Go, brother. You gotta go, man.
我们下辈子再见吧
I'll see you in the next life.
真见鬼
Bollocks.
快闪开 快闪开
Move over! Move over!
我们得走了
We gotta go!
我们得走了 快
Yo, we gotta go now!
它们来了 凯奇
They're coming, Cage.
来呀 你们这些混蛋
Come on, you bastards! Come on!
重新装弹
Reload.
重新装弹 重新装弹
Reload. Reload.
它们过来了
We got incoming!
快点儿
Come on!
凯奇
Cage!
你来控制飞船
You have to take over!
瑞塔
Rita!
加速 加速
Punch it! Punch it!
这不是最惨的
We've been through worse.
好了
Okay.
它在那儿
It's there.
在水里 那儿
In the water. There.
是个阿尔法
That's an Alpha.
一会儿我负责把它引开
I'm gonna draw that thing away.
你负责杀掉欧米伽
You kill the Omega.
不
No.
你挪不了几步就会被它杀掉 凯奇
You won't make it 10 feet before that thing kills you, Cage.
- 我能做到 - 拿着手榴弹
- I can do it. - Take the grenades.
我能做到
I can do it.
听我说 听我说
Listen to me. Listen to me.
这次我们俩谁都逃不了
Neither one of us is getting out of here.
谢谢你
Thank you...
让我能坚持到现在
for getting me this far.
你是个好男人 凯奇
You're a good man, Cage.
但愿能有机会好好了解你
I wish I had the chance to know you better.
欢迎来到伦敦 少校
Welcome to London, major.
我是蒙哥马利下士
I'm Corporal Montgomery
布里格姆将军新闻办公室的联络官
your liaison to General Brigham's press office.
很高兴你能来
Very good to have you.
你看新闻了吗
Have you heard the news? Isn't it brilliant?
走向胜利
就在今天黎明之前
Just before sunrise this morning...
巴黎探测到一股强大的能量波
a large surge of energy was detected in Paris.
我们虽然还没有查明原因到底是什么
We do not know exactly what this signifies.
但是结果却表明
But the result appears to be
我们的敌人已经完全丧失了战斗能力
a total collapse of the enemy's capacity to fight.
布里格姆将军
联合防御部队指挥官
俄国和中国的军队正在横扫欧洲
Russian and Chinese troops are now moving across Europe...
联合防御部队新闻发布会
一路所向披靡
without resistance.
明天 我们将挺进西部前线
Tomorrow, we advance on the western front.
相信我们一定取得胜利
We believe we are marching to claim victory
为我们自己
for ourselves...
为我们所爱的人
for our loved ones,
为我们的同胞
for our countrymen...
也为了整个人类
for the entire human race.
你们是干什么的
What are you? Sound off!
我们是战士
I'm a warrior!
- 战士该干什么 - 战斗
- What do warriors do? - Kill!
- What are you gonna do? - Kill!
你不可能参加过20场战斗
You have not been in 20 battles.
当然有
I have too.
明天一到海滩 你肯定会吓傻的
You're gonna dump your load the second you hit the beach.
拜托 你们俩能不能把臭嘴闭上
How about you two go get yourselves a nice hot cup of shut-the-hell-up!
真幽默 小妞
You funny, girl.
但我打赌 明天我会破纪录的
I bet you I set some kind of record tomorrow.
是逃跑最快记录吧
Fastest time running backwards, Ford,
别踩到自己拉的屎
slipping in your own shit.
你们是干什么的
What are you? Sound off!
我们是战士
I'm a warrior!
- 战士该干什么 - 战斗
- What do warriors do? - Kill!
立正
Attention!
怎么了
Yes?
有什么事吗
What do you want?
导演   道格·里曼
编剧   克里斯托弗·麦考利  杰兹·巴特沃斯  约翰-亨利·巴特沃斯
制片人
艾文·斯托夫
制片人  汤姆·莱瑟利
杰弗瑞·希尔佛
制片人   格里高利·贾格布斯
杰森·霍夫斯
执行制片人
道格·里曼
大卫·巴提斯
执行制片人
斯蒂文·摩纽钦
乔比·哈罗德
执行制片人
福原秀实
和  布鲁斯·伯曼
联合制片人
蒂姆·刘易斯
金·温特
根据樱坂洋原著小说“杀戮轮回”改编
汤姆·克鲁斯
明日边缘
艾米莉·布朗特
比尔·帕克斯顿
布兰登·格里森
诺亚·泰勒
基克·盖瑞
德拉古米尔·米希克
夏洛特·莱利
约纳斯·阿姆斯特朗
弗兰兹·德拉梅
羽田昌义
托尼·魏
摄影指导
迪昂·毕比
美术指导
奥利弗·斯库尔
剪辑  詹姆斯·赫伯特
劳拉·詹宁斯
选角导演
露辛达·塞森
服装设计
凯特·霍利
视觉特效总监
尼克·戴维斯
原创音乐
克里斯托弗·贝克
音响特效
朱利安·乔丹
华纳兄弟电影公司
荣誉出品
携手献映
威秀电影公司
拉特派克-沙丘娱乐
联袂制作
三艺娱乐 承制
碧日制片公司
倾力支持
道格·里曼 作品
无聊老生制作  谢谢各位观赏